smokersnews.com 2006-12-29

# Smokers News Privacy Statement

##  Privacy Statement for Cigarette Smokers News

We care about your on-line experience and your privacy. The **Cigarette Smokers News** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. This privacy statement discloses our practices for the gathering and use of information from visitors to our Web site, Cigarette Smokers News and from people who register for services that we offer online. 

The **Cigarette Smokers News** :   
1> provides a link to this Privacy Statement on all pages that ask for personal information   
2> will not release personal identifying information about you without first obtaining consent   
3> will not knowingly collect or use personal identifying information from children younger than 13 without parental consent 

We may use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. Your IP address is also used to gather broad demographic information.

We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we don't use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information. 

We arecurrently using registration forms as part of the **Cigarette Smokers News**. We do ask users to submit suggestions for future featured sites via email and require users to give us contact information (like their name, email, and postal address). We use customer contact information from the email registration to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners. The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below. 

We may use demographic and customer profile information to tailor the visitors' experience at our site, showing them content that we think might interest them and displaying the content according to their preferences. We share this information with advertisers only on an aggregate, anonymous basis and not on an individual basis. 

###  External Links

This site contains links to other sites. The **Cigarette Smokers News** is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

###  Public Forums

This site may make chat rooms and/or message boards available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

###  Choice/Opt-Out 

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from our partners, and us . This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

  1. You can send email to [remove@smokersnews.com](mailto:remove@smokersnews.com?subject=Remove%20from%20Cigarette%20Smokers%20News%20Site)

##  Contacting the Web Site 

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:   

Vic Bilson  
Cigarette Smokers News  
P.O. Box 20538  
Wichita, KS 67208  
eMail Contact
